ending
Boring days with no time to spare
You're a big boy, you mutter
Whenever you lose sight of what's important
I'm wrong when I win
The first one
The first one.
The 4th one
[Hajime Shacho ending]
Oh, wait a minute, wait a minute.
Yoshimura Naru but gross
Aaaaah!
OK.
Hang in there.
I can do it, I can do it, I can do it.
Nine, ten, eleven, twelve.
Okay.
Okay, Yui, please say a few words before the next V-swing.
Okay, now it's time for the last event!
The last event of the day, all nine of us tried jumping rope together!
Then, Harurun, please do the V-shake.
Yes, ma'am.
The last event is the big jump rope!
Can we do it in time?
Please watch the VTR.
And now, the last event of the day!
Girls' challenge with one heart!
So far, we've had individual competitions and team competitions, but now it's time for everyone to come together as one.
But in the end, we're all going to unite our hearts and minds together.At the end of the day, we all have to work together as one.
I hope that we can all play as a team.
And this time
Mr. Odakyu really looks like a gym teacher.
The number of times you've challenged us this time, right?
47 times, the same as Mr. Sakuma's age.
Forty-seven times.
but you have 10 minutes to complete it.
That's close enough.
He says there's only 10 minutes left to rent this place.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up, 47 times.
I see... we pushed it back an hour or something... or we got stopped by the guerrilla train on the way.
Please don't film me in the store.
Were you scared?
Why not?
Can I get a shot of you with this pair around here?
Was there such a thing?
Yes, there was.
I was scared.
Come on, you!
You're early.
I didn't know.
But even with nine guys, 47 times is a lot of work.
Clear this! Everyone's already counting on this place for future ruff ruff ruff!
The other day, the girls at All Nights Fuji flew it like 20 something times.
I only flew 20 or so times!I only flew like 20 times or something.
Good luck with one thing in mind!
Okay, let's do it!
Maybe a little higher?
Would it be stuck?
In high school, if a guy gets 180 or something, yeah.
I'm 165 at the highest.
Okay, that's our 10-minute challenge!
Lastly, Mr. Sakumo, one last word to all of you.
One for all!
All for one!
Hiroaka!
(Natsume just said "Hiroaka" in a low voice.
Maybe it was more like...
Shinjiro Yamashita
This is rugby, right?
It's a rugby video!
Guys, let's just ignore this guy.
But one-form all bones, if it were now, he'd be a hero.
Okay, then, everyone, let's try the first one, please!
Aaaaah!
I knew it!
This summer... Yoshimura?
Yoshimura fell for it.
That's why I think we should all speak up for each other.
More than you think... Raise your momo... Momo, momo... Raise your momo...
Here we go.
Come on, go ahead, go ahead, or I can't see you.
What do you want me to say?
Come on.Seino.
So the person in the middle has to fly on trust.
That's why you have to trust them.
Can you go this one?
About two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight fast.
I see. I see.
Okay, let's go for the second try. Go ahead.
Ready.
All right!
Yes!
Oh!
I can do it!
That's great!
I can do it! I can do it! I can do it!
You can do it! This is it!
Oh! Oh, my gosh! Oh, my gosh!
Oh! Oh, my God!
Ah!
Yoshimura! I'm not looking for the culprit!
Someone was looking for the culprit first.
That was Yoshimura.
No, but Yoshimura's a bit on the small side.
They're all 18 years old.
The minus one is getting tired, so it's a little low.
I'm sure they'll be fine, just as they are.
It's true, I kick my legs.
And, you know, the closer you are, the harder it gets a little bit.
That's right.
Seeeeee!
All right!Okay!
Yoshimura, you're a little behind on your jumps, aren't you?
Five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten!
Okay, 10!
I can do it, I can do it, I can do it.
Nagamatsu, Fujisaki's getting a little tired.
Yoshimura, you're lifting your leg out of a sense of responsibility.
Judgment!
Go for it!
Oh, great.
28, 29, 30!
31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40!
Oh, my God!
Everyone got 40!
I can't believe I made it to 40... or vice versa.
I wouldn't be tired if it had been single digits.
But I'm tired because I'm at 40.
Six minutes left, ladies and gentlemen.
Mr. Sakama, aren't you 20 years old?
No, I'm not! You're not that young!
What do I look like?
I've been through a lot.
We've only got about 5 minutes left.
If it gets hard, just think of it as tightening your thighs.
I see... I see.
We're running out of time. Let's go!
I can do it!
Can you do it?
It's true, the future family's timing is tight.
Kashikurachi, time is tight.We're on a tight schedule.
How's it going?
Four!
Ready!
One, two, go for it!
Three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
This one's pretty strenuous for a little kid.
Twelve. Thirteen. Fourteen. Fifteen.
Neck! You're holding her hair down so it doesn't get caught.
18 19 20 Peaches!
How are you hi
Ready, go!
He's done it!
I'm in, alies I'm learning body
How are you algorithms
halfway down
Three, three, three, three!
That's great.
No, it's great.
That's great!
I told you to lift up your thighs.
You!
Clear, clear, clear! This is great!
That's great, that's great, that's great, that's great, that's great.
You did it!
And you know what, we've been at it all morning. Sports day.
It's not like we're suddenly taking all these pictures today.
Saito, we were in the middle of it.
We were on the verge.
I mean, his right leg is still stuck.Um, I'm not sure if I'm missing my right foot.
Saito well
So, I cleared it on the fourth try!
That's great!
Ruff Ruff is in safe hands.
That must have been tough.
It must have been tough.
I thought I'd lost it.
I was thinking of leaving Ruff Ruff.
You know, the owner...
The owner won't stop me, so I'm leaving.
I did my best. I want to do my best.
But to be honest, it was really hard to be in the woods.
We were at the very end, and everyone was facing this way.
So he was coming this way more and more.
That's why the woods are turning more and more, and that guy...
No, he's not in the woods anymore.
He was jumping up and down.
He had a lot of energy. That's great.
Who said the last one?
Yes, Mr. Sasaki.
Sasaki-san's yes.
11, 12, 13!
That's great.
Did you think about saying "yes" before you did it?
I was vice president this year.
I was the owner's mentor.
Mentor?
Mr. Sakuma, I knew this was a production.
I wasn't listening.I haven't heard anything.
Pleased to meet you.
No, that's great. That was a team effort. My legs were at their limits.
I thought you could only jump three times, or two times, or three times.
I thought I could only jump three times, but everyone else jumped quite a bit. Everyone jumped 10 or 30 times. So I was at my limit.
When I did it once for 40 jumps, my legs were close to the limit, even Hayashi's legs were close to the limit.
It was pretty close to the limit. He was jumping so much.
He must have been doing it since this morning.
Yoshimura, actually, you were the one who did 40 times.
Please don't look at me.
There might not have been.
Was it pressure?
It was bad, pressure.
I was getting tired in the middle of the game.
I was in so much pain that I had already sprayed myself here.
Everyone was like that, but the older group.
You mean, the older group already smelled like sips?
Yes.
Fujisaki, too, because being in the very back means that the rope is very high.
After 40 times, I thought I was going to die.
But you got your hair caught.
No, I thought if I jumped, it would go like this, and then it would go sticky.
No, it wouldn't stop, that's for sure.
Oh, it stopped.
It wasn't like your hair got a little sticky.
That was good, wasn't it? Yes.
Yes. Now, it's time for the Ruff Ruff Sports King competition.
Let's have him announce the grand prize for the best effort.
Mr. Sakuma, please.
First of all, this block.First of all, this block.
This block, then, is the grand prize for good luck to all.
Yay!
After listing the grand prize for good effort for everyone, you mean who did the best this time?
Uh, yeah, I guess.
But, you know, this time, two people.
Hayashi and Sasaki.
I guess.
Throughout the whole film, you know. I did my best, and I thought it was kind of, oh, interesting.
Thank you very much.
But it was great. Everyone's character came out.
Just a little bit, so just Kuritani.
Just Kuritani, let's discuss it again in a little while sometime.
It's easy to stay longer.
Isn't it better not to say "stay longer"?
As a mental caregiver, Sakuma-san.
No, I'm not. I'm a producer.
I'm not a mental health care worker.
I'm a producer.
I've been getting a lot of flak from people on Yahoo!
Well, it happens, doesn't it?
By the time you come before the show, you've been hit mentally, and during the live broadcast...
Wait a minute.
That's happened, hasn't it?
Things like that.
No, no, no.
Thank you for watching to the end, the battle to determine the king of sports.
The last message is for this person.
Mise-sa
a bearbear (animal)
anteater
ri
is
tooth